<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>thoughts on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/thoughts/</link><description>Recent content in thoughts on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the price of a ghost</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-price-of-a-ghost/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-price-of-a-ghost/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve said it before and i&amp;rsquo;ll say it again: i owe ghost energy drinks my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree.
ghost energy drinks were marketed to me originally in 2020/2021 as hype with specific ingredients that touted the idea of more focused brain activity for lengthy durations of time, which was the perfect thing for a guy pulling late nighters in college like me.
(not because i was studying particularly hard, but rather because reconciling the lifestyle of a gamer with the necessity of being a university-level engineering student came with its fair share of problems that affected my sleep heavily.</description></item><item><title>GLP-1's are here in a big way</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/glp-1s-are-here-in-a-big-way/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/glp-1s-are-here-in-a-big-way/</guid><description>i think since the new year has started i&amp;rsquo;ve been getting more advertisements for glp-1 medications for weight loss.
it must have something to do with new years' resolutions. either that or i&amp;rsquo;m being specifically targeted, which is a very real possibility. either way, i feel like i haven&amp;rsquo;t seen ozempic, wegovy, and zepbound taking as much prominence as i have in previous months at all, despite knowing about ozempic since last year around june.</description></item><item><title>the new savage tier</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-new-savage-tier/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-new-savage-tier/</guid><description>today on january 6th 2026, the new savage tier of ffxiv released.
for the uninitiated, this means ffxiv players are quite happy today. some players get to spend more time with their &amp;ldquo;static&amp;rdquo;, a dedicated group of raid buddies. other people will be slumming it in &amp;ldquo;Party Finder&amp;rdquo;, making the most of their time with randoms.
i spend a lot of time raiding in ffxiv, so this is exciting for me.</description></item><item><title>can you keep up?</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/can-you-keep-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/can-you-keep-up/</guid><description>the thing about good habits, and life in general really, is it feels like all you&amp;rsquo;re ever doing is keeping up.
it&amp;rsquo;s a battle of attrition against the natural flow of life, that we all undertake knowing we&amp;rsquo;re going to lose someday.
despite that, it&amp;rsquo;s all we can do, to call this life a &amp;ldquo;life&amp;rdquo;, to continue making what we can of each day.
it&amp;rsquo;s often quite demotivating to remember that things are tasks that you have to keep up.</description></item><item><title>good ole american breakfast</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/good-ole-american-breakfast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/good-ole-american-breakfast/</guid><description>what is an american breakfast to you?
to a lot of american diner restaurants, it means pancakes, bacon, eggs, sausages, hash browns, and even sandwiches. and even among that, what kind of eggs? sausage links or sausage patties? grits or hash browns? let&amp;rsquo;s not even bother getting into the amount of things you can add to pancakes, and the varieties of breakfast sandwiches and pastries exist.
the amount of variety is endless.</description></item><item><title>any austin the video essayist</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/any-austin-the-video-essayist/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/any-austin-the-video-essayist/</guid><description>have you ever heard of any austin?
he&amp;rsquo;s a youtube video essayist who makes commenataries on video games about things that are outstandingly mundane, like power lines in GTA 5, hydrology, and unemployment surveys.
i&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by his content. his cadence and pacing, especially, is uniquely captivating in its presentation. i&amp;rsquo;ve since exhausted his catalog of skyrim related videos, and found other skyrim video essayists EXTREMELY wanting.
something about them is just too nerdy to follow.</description></item><item><title>and yet over and over</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/and-yet-over-and-over/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/and-yet-over-and-over/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;m pretty bad with my sleep schedule.
i think i&amp;rsquo;ve written about this one before but it bears repeating because it is so pervasive of a problem for me.
how do you reconcile staying up because the rest of the world is up playing games and having fun with needing to be up the next day?
at some point, something has to give. i wonder when that time will come for me.</description></item></channel></rss>