<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>thoughts on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/thoughts/</link><description>Recent content in thoughts on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>taking it easy</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/taking-it-easy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/taking-it-easy/</guid><description>are you easy-going? or are you a gas-gas-gas type?
nowadays more than ever,
it&amp;rsquo;s hard to convince yourself to take things easy.
we live in a culture of go-getters and efficiency.
i believe in the ebb and flow of life&amp;rsquo;s rhythm,
and in the idea of equivalent exchange.
good times simply must follow bad ones.
so when i recognize that times are tough,
and effort must be exerted to see success,</description></item><item><title>home-cooked meals</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/home-cooked-meals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/home-cooked-meals/</guid><description>home-cooked meals are just the best, right?
at this point in my life, i live at home
and enjoy the benefits of, for most meals,
being able to eat home-cooked meals from my parents.
for a while i&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to get more into
cooking regularly, but there are some issues i have
with cooking in this particular home:
storage issues with existing items making food for more than one person trying recipes with ingredients that probably won&amp;rsquo;t be used frequently not to mention the natural struggle of needing to</description></item><item><title>in spite of logic</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-spite-of-logic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-spite-of-logic/</guid><description>you ever do something you know you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be doing?
i&amp;rsquo;m currently playing through Final Fantasy VII Rebirth,
a game with over a hundred hours of content inside,
but also holding the capability to be finished in under 30 hours.
my reason for playing this game is because i have a concert
for the FFVII Rebirth Orchestra this saturday the 17th
wherein spoilers for the game will be shown.
therefore, i need to complete the game as fast as possible</description></item><item><title>pets have regen properties</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/pets-have-regen-properties/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/pets-have-regen-properties/</guid><description>when the chips are down, a cat can change it all.
i&amp;rsquo;ve been taking trips to take care of
my brother&amp;rsquo;s cat recently while he&amp;rsquo;s away.
i have to drive 30 minutes there and back (1hr total),
so it&amp;rsquo;s a little annoying when i&amp;rsquo;m on the way there,
thinking about how i have -1hr minimum in my day.
but then, i see the cat.
sweetie on the countertop.</description></item><item><title>notepad gripes</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/notepad-gripes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/notepad-gripes/</guid><description>i got some gripes with notepad.
specifically, notepad on windows 11.
to start, one thing that&amp;rsquo;s good is that it supports dark mode.
i don&amp;rsquo;t know if that was there in windows 10.
if it was, i was not appreciative enough of it to acknowledge it.
i use notepad to write these blogposts (editing .md files),
and for some god-forsaken reason, closing the notepad window
does not close the files that have been opened by notepad.</description></item><item><title>sonny boy</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/sonny-boy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/sonny-boy/</guid><description>one of my favorite anime of all time is &amp;ldquo;Sonny Boy&amp;rdquo;.
sonny boy is about a class of middle schoolers,
focused on a boy named Nagara.
as they approach the end of their middle school days,
they are suddenly transported into an alternate dimension
where the laws of the world are as fickle as they are mysterious.
nagara, mizuho, and kamabiko, from Sonny Boy.</description></item><item><title>learning experiences</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-experiences/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-experiences/</guid><description>sometimes, you just gotta take it on the chin.
a lesson i&amp;rsquo;ve had to learn many times in life is that
things aren&amp;rsquo;t always going to go as planned.
and when they don&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s important to persevere.
on the same side of that coin,
it is important to interpret your losses not strictly as negative,
but as learning experiences and as things you can learn from.
your losses become way more productive once you can do this.</description></item></channel></rss>