<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gaming on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/gaming/</link><description>Recent content in gaming on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>deadlock and dota 2</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/deadlock-and-dota-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/deadlock-and-dota-2/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve recently been playing valve&amp;rsquo;s unreleased hero shooter, Deadlock.
my background is that i played a decent (400-600hrs) amount of overwatch/overwatch 2,
and a pretty good amount (~2000hrs) of Dota 2, Valve&amp;rsquo;s flagship MOBA.
i&amp;rsquo;m enjoying the game a lot! some of the visuals in-game are a little
rough around the edges, but for the most part, i like the aesthetic they&amp;rsquo;re going for.
i believe the name of the map is the Rotten Apple, in a kind of 50&amp;rsquo;s NYC vibe.</description></item><item><title>running it down mid</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/running-it-down-mid/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/running-it-down-mid/</guid><description>if you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been in a situation where the goal is clear,
and you know with certainty what you must do to succeed,
yet you still choose to do something that&amp;rsquo;s not only
NOT what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to do, but even the exact OPPOSITE
of what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to be doing,
you have &amp;ldquo;ran it down.&amp;rdquo;
running it down mid is a term that comes from MOBAs
like League of Legends and Dota 2, where there&amp;rsquo;s</description></item><item><title>in spite of logic</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-spite-of-logic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-spite-of-logic/</guid><description>you ever do something you know you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be doing?
i&amp;rsquo;m currently playing through Final Fantasy VII Rebirth,
a game with over a hundred hours of content inside,
but also holding the capability to be finished in under 30 hours.
my reason for playing this game is because i have a concert
for the FFVII Rebirth Orchestra this saturday the 17th
wherein spoilers for the game will be shown.
therefore, i need to complete the game as fast as possible</description></item><item><title>learning experiences</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-experiences/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-experiences/</guid><description>sometimes, you just gotta take it on the chin.
a lesson i&amp;rsquo;ve had to learn many times in life is that
things aren&amp;rsquo;t always going to go as planned.
and when they don&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s important to persevere.
on the same side of that coin,
it is important to interpret your losses not strictly as negative,
but as learning experiences and as things you can learn from.
your losses become way more productive once you can do this.</description></item><item><title>console gaming</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/console-gaming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/console-gaming/</guid><description>are you a console gamer?
for a while i would have random thoughts of
being someone who plays games on a console
in addition to playing PC games.
just seemed like a good mix. like a healthy balance.
&amp;ldquo;i can do console exclusives AND play PC games with friends.
win win situation! aside from buying the console.&amp;rdquo;
i wanted to grab a PS5 when they came out but
obviously supply chain issues stepped in</description></item><item><title>you got games on your phone?</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/you-got-games-on-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/you-got-games-on-your-phone/</guid><description>you got games on your phone?
i know a few people who are actually really into mobile gaming.
and i mean gacha games, mainly HoYoVerse. they seem to be pretty popular.
i tried genshin out a few times and the music is actually quite relaxing.
but i could never get into the &amp;ldquo;playing it daily&amp;rdquo; part of it.
it seemed like a huge chore and not enjoyable for me.
i thought this was a reflection at one point in time</description></item><item><title>shared suffering</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/shared-suffering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/shared-suffering/</guid><description>one of my favorite concepts ever has to be shared suffering.
when groups of people go through the same slog of bullshit,
and they all know amongst themselves that none of them are enjoying it,
but they gotta do it because it&amp;rsquo;s a requirement for something else.
as you could have probably guessed by now,
my primary example is from final fantasy xiv.
in it, there was once this grueling slog of a set of dungeons</description></item></channel></rss>