<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gaming on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/gaming/</link><description>Recent content in gaming on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>legend of zelda wind waker</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/legend-of-zelda-wind-waker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/legend-of-zelda-wind-waker/</guid><description>remember the Nintendo GameCube?
the GameCube was host to many legendary Nintendo titles,
like Super Smash Bros. Melee and Mario Kart Double Dash.
however, if you ask me what was a standout hit from that time,
i&amp;rsquo;ve gotta go with The Legend of Zelda: Wind Waker.
Link in Wind Waker, riding the King of Red Lions. in Wind Waker, you control Link as he navigates across the seas</description></item><item><title>i finished disco elysium</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/i-finished-disco-elysium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/i-finished-disco-elysium/</guid><description>today i finished disco elysium!
it was a thoughtful and beautiful game.
easily my top 5 of all time.
in the beginning of playing this game,
i thought that the dialogue was unwieldy
and laborious to read, that it was somehow
something that &amp;ldquo;ought to be unnecessary.&amp;rdquo;
this was conditioning from the previous games i had played,
which, despite having narratives i can stand behind,
simply were not up to the standard of disco&amp;rsquo;s writing.</description></item><item><title>decisions decisions</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/decisions-decisions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/decisions-decisions/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve been playing a lot more Disco Elysium lately.
in the game, you play as a detective who is guided by his internal aspects,
like &amp;ldquo;pain threshold&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;reaction speed&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;visual calculus&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;inland empire&amp;rdquo;,
on your journey to solve the case of a hanged man and your retrograde amnesia.
it&amp;rsquo;s having me think a lot about how my self-talk works.
&amp;ldquo;volition&amp;rdquo; in this game is your ability to resist temptation,</description></item><item><title>web gaming</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/web-gaming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/web-gaming/</guid><description>did you play browser games when you were younger?
i&amp;rsquo;m not sure if kids these days play browser games anymore.
but i&amp;rsquo;m talking websites like addictinggames.com,
stickpage.com, kongregate.com, and armorgames.com.
i would go on these sites after school in elementary
and just play random bullshit games for hours.
it was awesome.
you might have even heard of andyslife.org,
which is the secret site we had to use at catholic school</description></item><item><title>the razer deathadder line of gaming mice</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-razer-deathadder-line-of-gaming-mice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-razer-deathadder-line-of-gaming-mice/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve long been a fan of the razer deathadder line of gaming mice.
my first razer mouse was a razer naga hex, which was very useful when i was playing Dota 2 as it was made to accommodate the 6 slot inventory of potential active items in the game. after that, i had a deathadder elite original, but gave it up because i wanted more side buttons. the shape was something i would never forget, however.</description></item><item><title>genuine dedication or utter foolishness?</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/genuine-dedication-or-utter-foolishness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/genuine-dedication-or-utter-foolishness/</guid><description>how long have you ever spent doing a single thing?
i don&amp;rsquo;t mean breathing. i mean something that requires active
consciousness and participation that you can&amp;rsquo;t do without trying.
something like writing a manuscript, or reading a book,
or doing something outside, or even doing work.
today, i spent 10 hours playing deadlock.
so.. yeah. but it was a hell of a saturday.
i had a great time.
thanks for reading today&amp;rsquo;s post.</description></item><item><title>in-game names</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-game-names/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-game-names/</guid><description>if you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with igns, or in-game names,
they&amp;rsquo;re a way to call someone in a game. their username.
or their character name. or their display name.
my first username that i can remember was Project_Star,
back on a korean mmo that i forget the name of (not MapleStory).
i used a lot of different names like Project_Silver, Project_WAR,
and in the present day, ProjectG (for gabe).
in-game names are fun because they&amp;rsquo;re what people choose most of the time</description></item></channel></rss>