<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gaming on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/gaming/</link><description>Recent content in gaming on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>you got games on your phone?</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/you-got-games-on-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/you-got-games-on-your-phone/</guid><description>you got games on your phone?
i know a few people who are actually really into mobile gaming.
and i mean gacha games, mainly HoYoVerse. they seem to be pretty popular.
i tried genshin out a few times and the music is actually quite relaxing.
but i could never get into the &amp;ldquo;playing it daily&amp;rdquo; part of it.
it seemed like a huge chore and not enjoyable for me.
i thought this was a reflection at one point in time</description></item><item><title>shared suffering</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/shared-suffering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/shared-suffering/</guid><description>one of my favorite concepts ever has to be shared suffering.
when groups of people go through the same slog of bullshit,
and they all know amongst themselves that none of them are enjoying it,
but they gotta do it because it&amp;rsquo;s a requirement for something else.
as you could have probably guessed by now,
my primary example is from final fantasy xiv.
in it, there was once this grueling slog of a set of dungeons</description></item><item><title>attention and hunger</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/attention-and-hunger/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/attention-and-hunger/</guid><description>do you ever lose your sense of hunger when focused?
i think it&amp;rsquo;s super interesting that this happens.
dr. k spoke about this once in the lens of ayurvedic teaching.
something along the lines of your attention being a limited resource,
like you have 100 attention points to spend on any amount of things at a time.
so if you manage to focus so intently on one thing,
you actually minimize the capacity to have your attention grabbed</description></item><item><title>changing things up</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/changing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/changing-things-up/</guid><description>do you ever find it interesting how we feel the need to change things up every now and then?
as humans, we crave the new and get bored of the old..
such ingratitude. after all the times the old has saved our lives!
like when we brush our teeth! or remember to take our meds!
it could be a superpower in its own right to never get bored of something, couldn&amp;rsquo;t it?</description></item><item><title>final fantasy xiv</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/final-fantasy-xiv/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/final-fantasy-xiv/</guid><description>i used to play a lot of final fantasy xiv, the MMORPG of the final fantasy series.
i got into it back in 2020 when my senior at UIUC, jared, invited me to play with him.
he was trying to rope as many people as he possibly could into the game
because, unsurprisingly, MMOs are a lot more fun with good friends to play with.
i humored him on the idea because in my childhood and elementary school years,</description></item></channel></rss>