<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gooberverse on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/</link><description>Recent content in gooberverse on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the end of the day</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-end-of-the-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-end-of-the-day/</guid><description>what&amp;rsquo;s your ideal end to the day like?
one that&amp;rsquo;s particularly hard for me to beat
is taking a good dump after a long day of eating good food.
which might sound crass, but hear me out; it&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate relief.
after travelling and seeing the sights with your friends and walking around,
talking and eating food at restaurants you&amp;rsquo;ve never been to before,
you end up back in the comfort of your own home, your intestines churning.</description></item><item><title>the end of the day</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/today/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/today/</guid><description>what&amp;rsquo;s your ideal end to the day like?
one that&amp;rsquo;s particularly hard for me to beat
is taking a good dump after a long day of eating good food.
which might sound crass, but hear me out; it&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate relief.
after travelling and seeing the sights with your friends and walking around,
talking and eating food at restaurants you&amp;rsquo;ve never been to before,
you end up back in the comfort of your own home, your intestines churning.</description></item><item><title>being an npc</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/being-an-npc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/being-an-npc/</guid><description>i was thinking today about what it&amp;rsquo;s like being an npc.
in the figurative sense of being an npc with reference to other people,
and literally being an npc in like a video game or a movie or something.
like in a scene where the main character overhears something important
while they&amp;rsquo;re at a bar because two dudes are having a conversation that&amp;rsquo;s
just a little too loud, i&amp;rsquo;m imagining those guys getting interviewing like it&amp;rsquo;s</description></item><item><title>talking to yourself in traffic</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-yourself-in-traffic/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-yourself-in-traffic/</guid><description>do you ever talk to yourself? i recommend it. it can be quite fun.
some of the greatest laughs i&amp;rsquo;ve ever had were from jokes i said while talking to myself.
i was talking to myself earlier today when i was driving home from a bakery.
the car in front of me was going amazingly slowly,
but we were at that vague distance from where i would left turn that it&amp;rsquo;s like,</description></item><item><title>sounds and being weird</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/sounds-and-being-weird/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/sounds-and-being-weird/</guid><description>anyone else listen to stuff that only they listen to, and none of your friends can relate?
there&amp;rsquo;s a few things i&amp;rsquo;ve found that basically only i know myself to listen to:
ambient sound videos (walking in tokyo, library study asmr, sounds of a mcdonald&amp;rsquo;s) animal crossing music for fun (i downloaded local versions to listen to on spotify) the same thing that isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily a full song for an obscenely long time once when grinding uni work, i listened to Dark Fantasy by Kanye West but just the first part where they literally go &amp;ldquo;can we get much higher so high oh oh oh&amp;rdquo; for 30 minutes straight work/study jazz streams on youtube that kind of don&amp;rsquo;t even feel like real music my coworkers and i were going to lunch one day and i was the driver,</description></item><item><title>my coffee journey</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/my-coffee-journey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/my-coffee-journey/</guid><description>last year in January, i decided that i needed an addiction.
a new one, not just the usual childish addictions like videogames and anime.
no, i needed an adult addiction that was so powerful that it carries with it
an air of haughtiness that blows away all who dare question its validity.
so i decided to get into coffee.
i decided to get into making pour-over coffee at home for a few reasons:</description></item><item><title>final fantasy xiv</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/final-fantasy-xiv/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/final-fantasy-xiv/</guid><description>i used to play a lot of final fantasy xiv, the MMORPG of the final fantasy series.
i got into it back in 2020 when my senior at UIUC, jared, invited me to play with him.
he was trying to rope as many people as he possibly could into the game
because, unsurprisingly, MMOs are a lot more fun with good friends to play with.
i humored him on the idea because in my childhood and elementary school years,</description></item><item><title>pictures and photography</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/pictures-and-photography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/pictures-and-photography/</guid><description>we all go on random youtube binges right?
the ones where it&amp;rsquo;s a topic that you&amp;rsquo;ve briefly touched in the past,
and you never got fully into but seemed interesting at the time.
one of those for me is professional photography.
as someone who has done a fairly minimal amount of research into the
more detailed parts of the workflow of it all,
f numbers, apertures, shooting speeds, lens sizes, digital and film,</description></item><item><title>talking to people</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-people/</guid><description>how do you feel about being at parties with strangers?
do you go into it thinking it&amp;rsquo;s an exciting chance to meet new people?
are you anxious about having to answer questions about who you are?
every time i&amp;rsquo;m put in that situation, i wonder why i tend more to anxiety
rather than curiosity.
was it easier that way at some point in time? &amp;hellip;easier for who?
it&amp;rsquo;s quite relatable, actually.</description></item><item><title>thinking and doing</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/thinking-and-doing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/thinking-and-doing/</guid><description>thinking and doing are two modes of operation that i consider when talking about work.
this is to say i choose not to apply it with something whimsical or less &amp;ldquo;important&amp;rdquo;,
like my attitude with cooking eggs, or how i decide what clothes to wear.
&amp;ldquo;thinking&amp;rdquo; is when you make a plan of action to do something.
i think about it most when doing work at my job,
because usually to do my job, i need to at least plan a little bit.</description></item><item><title>mashing</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/mashing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/mashing/</guid><description>if you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with what &amp;ldquo;mashing&amp;rdquo; is, i&amp;rsquo;ll try to explain.
&amp;ldquo;mashing&amp;rdquo; is when there is a logical way to reach a solution,
but instead of going on that path,
you guess a solution until you either give up or it miraculously works.
in the context of fighting games, when you get knocked down to the ground,
you have to respond to a multitude of possible attacks from the opponent:</description></item><item><title>learning the ropes</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-the-ropes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-the-ropes/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;learning the ropes&amp;rdquo; is very much mentally associated in my brain with &amp;ldquo;day 2&amp;rdquo;. why? in swords and sandals II: emperor&amp;rsquo;s reign, every day has a title associated with it. day 1 is &amp;ldquo;glorious freedom&amp;rdquo;. day 2 is &amp;ldquo;learning the ropes.&amp;rdquo; so, this is today&amp;rsquo;s title.
i mentioned last time that i wanted to at least roughly jot down the steps it took to get this webserver up and running, so i&amp;rsquo;ll use this time to recall them.</description></item><item><title>space pilot 3000</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/space-pilot-3000/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/space-pilot-3000/</guid><description>the title of today&amp;rsquo;s post, the very first one, is from futurama, a show about an average dude named Fry who gets cryogenically frozen in the year 2000 and wakes up in the year 3000 to earth being an interstellar civilization. following his job as a pizza delivery boy in the past, he becomes a spaceship delivery boy in the future, hence the name &amp;ldquo;space pilot 3000&amp;rdquo;. i always liked the name, it just sounds neat.</description></item><item><title>right now</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/now/</guid><description>what am i up to? inspired by nownownow.com.
right now, i am
living in Illinois and enjoying the company of local, good friends writing software for infrared cameras playing Disco Elysium, Final Fantasy 7 Remake, and Street Fighter 6 reading Blood, Sweat, and Pixels by Jason Schreier and Endure by Alex Hutchinson trying to lift four times a week excitedly setting up this website〔´∇｀〕</description></item></channel></rss>