<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gooberverse on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/</link><description>Recent content in gooberverse on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>monthly calendars</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/monthly-calendars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/monthly-calendars/</guid><description>i used to not have any physical calendars because i felt i wasn&amp;rsquo;t organized enough to make use of a calendar.
then, at some point, i decided some calendars just look quite neat and they offer value on their own by acting as nice decoration.
helenpeanut&amp;rsquo;s 2024 calendar featuring Haikyuu!! characters. i have this one by helenpeanut featuring Haikyuu!! characters, which is an anime about highschoolers in Japan playing volleyball and trying to be the best in the country.</description></item><item><title>touching grass</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/touching-grass/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/touching-grass/</guid><description>have you ever been told to &amp;ldquo;touch grass&amp;rdquo;?
&amp;ldquo;touching grass&amp;rdquo; is a term used on the internet to tell people
that they need to go outside and re-align themselves with reality,
because their behavior on the internet is so outlandish and unreasonable
that it surely implies they haven&amp;rsquo;t spoken to a real human in some time.
&amp;ldquo;touching grass&amp;rdquo;, therefore, is something you can only do outside.
and with your real body, not a virtual one.</description></item><item><title>logic's new album</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/logics-new-album/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/logics-new-album/</guid><description>when i was in high school, i used to listen to Logic.
(and also for a bit in college)
my two favorite albums of his were Under Pressure and The Incredible True Story,
his freshman and sophomore albums that hearken me back to the days
of driving my friends to off-campus lunch in high school, bumping &amp;ldquo;Stainless&amp;rdquo; in the car.
after he released the Everybody album to divisive reviews,
he underwent an extremely corny arc where all his music just&amp;hellip; wasn&amp;rsquo;t hitting the same.</description></item><item><title>deadlock and dota 2</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/deadlock-and-dota-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/deadlock-and-dota-2/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve recently been playing valve&amp;rsquo;s unreleased hero shooter, Deadlock.
my background is that i played a decent (400-600hrs) amount of overwatch/overwatch 2,
and a pretty good amount (~2000hrs) of Dota 2, Valve&amp;rsquo;s flagship MOBA.
i&amp;rsquo;m enjoying the game a lot! some of the visuals in-game are a little
rough around the edges, but for the most part, i like the aesthetic they&amp;rsquo;re going for.
i believe the name of the map is the Rotten Apple, in a kind of 50&amp;rsquo;s NYC vibe.</description></item><item><title>where i'm at with reading right now</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/where-im-at-with-reading-right-now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/where-im-at-with-reading-right-now/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;m on the 2nd to last chapter of Blood, Sweat, and Pixels by Jason Schreier, videogame journalist. i got to this point a week or so ago, and i was thinking &amp;ldquo;man, maybe i should just sit down and finish this book. there&amp;rsquo;s only two chapters left!&amp;rdquo;
but this year i&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking more about the reading process, and reading to have read rather than trying to really sit with a book.</description></item><item><title>headaches and substances</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/headaches-and-substances/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/headaches-and-substances/</guid><description>when you get a headache, what do you do about it?
growing up, i never used ibuprofen or acetaminophen to cope with headaches.
i just assumed they would go away eventually. also being a boy mean thugging shit out.
in my adult years, however, i have opened the pill bottle a good amount of times.
that being said, my initial reaction to a headache is still not to reach for a substance.</description></item><item><title>the hidden cost of transitions</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-hidden-cost-of-transitions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-hidden-cost-of-transitions/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking recently about the hidden cost of transitions between activities.
when it comes to filling your day with things that you can look back on and be satisfied with, one thing that happens regardless of activity or action is the transition between A and B. this can be anything from driving home to changing clothes to just simply mentally preparing yourself. deceptively, these moments are where the time you intend on dedicating to the actual activity can be stolen.</description></item></channel></rss>