<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gooberverse on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/</link><description>Recent content in gooberverse on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>running it down mid</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/running-it-down-mid/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/running-it-down-mid/</guid><description>if you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been in a situation where the goal is clear,
and you know with certainty what you must do to succeed,
yet you still choose to do something that&amp;rsquo;s not only
NOT what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to do, but even the exact OPPOSITE
of what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to be doing,
you have &amp;ldquo;ran it down.&amp;rdquo;
running it down mid is a term that comes from MOBAs
like League of Legends and Dota 2, where there&amp;rsquo;s</description></item><item><title>awolnation wasn't the worst</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/awolnation-wasnt-the-worst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/awolnation-wasnt-the-worst/</guid><description>i don&amp;rsquo;t know what public opinion is on awolnation,
but i&amp;rsquo;d like to say i actually like their music.
undoubtedly their most famous track is &amp;ldquo;Sail&amp;rdquo; which terrorized
the internet and memes for the better part of a year around 2011.
following their success with &amp;ldquo;Sail&amp;rdquo;, they received deals from Valve
to make music packs for some of their games, like CS:GO and Dota 2.
in 2018, they released &amp;ldquo;Here Come the Runts&amp;rdquo;, which featured</description></item><item><title>ramen noodles as a meal</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/ramen-noodles-as-a-meal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/ramen-noodles-as-a-meal/</guid><description>do you enjoy eating ramen noodles?
i think part of me romanticizes ramen noodles
because of their association with anime and japan.
ichiraku ramen from Naruto just made it look so delicious.
kyuramen x tbaar wall art. shot with fuji x-t50. usually ramen stores will have different soup bases,
and you make your choice from there with toppings.
the soup bases are typically shio, shoyu, tonkotsu, and miso.</description></item><item><title>orchestra concerts</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/orchestra-concerts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/orchestra-concerts/</guid><description>you ever go to a symphony orchestra concert?
as a final fantasy fan, i&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to go
to a few &amp;ldquo;Distant Worlds&amp;rdquo; performances at the
Chicago Symphony Center on Michigan Avenue.
today, i went to see the FF7 Rebirth Symphony Orchestra
on their second date of their worldwide tour!
i had the pleasure of going with a couple of friends.
my view from the balcony.</description></item><item><title>odd obsessions</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/odd-obsessions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/odd-obsessions/</guid><description>odd obsessions are one of the easiest ways to get to know someone.
i&amp;rsquo;ve talked about talking to people before,
where my point was that we should be understanding that
the basis of many relationships can be around mundane things.
but when you and another person are both into a niche thing?
that&amp;rsquo;s when the magic happens, i think.
it depends on how weird it is, of course.
having an NBA buddy and having a stamp collection buddy;</description></item><item><title>taking it easy</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/taking-it-easy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/taking-it-easy/</guid><description>are you easy-going? or are you a gas-gas-gas type?
nowadays more than ever,
it&amp;rsquo;s hard to convince yourself to take things easy.
we live in a culture of go-getters and efficiency.
i believe in the ebb and flow of life&amp;rsquo;s rhythm,
and in the idea of equivalent exchange.
good times simply must follow bad ones.
so when i recognize that times are tough,
and effort must be exerted to see success,</description></item><item><title>home-cooked meals</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/home-cooked-meals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/home-cooked-meals/</guid><description>home-cooked meals are just the best, right?
at this point in my life, i live at home
and enjoy the benefits of, for most meals,
being able to eat home-cooked meals from my parents.
for a while i&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to get more into
cooking regularly, but there are some issues i have
with cooking in this particular home:
storage issues with existing items making food for more than one person trying recipes with ingredients that probably won&amp;rsquo;t be used frequently not to mention the natural struggle of needing to</description></item></channel></rss>