<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>can you keep up?</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/can-you-keep-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/can-you-keep-up/</guid><description>the thing about good habits, and life in general really, is it feels like all you&amp;rsquo;re ever doing is keeping up.
it&amp;rsquo;s a battle of attrition against the natural flow of life, that we all undertake knowing we&amp;rsquo;re going to lose someday.
despite that, it&amp;rsquo;s all we can do, to call this life a &amp;ldquo;life&amp;rdquo;, to continue making what we can of each day.
it&amp;rsquo;s often quite demotivating to remember that things are tasks that you have to keep up.</description></item><item><title>good ole american breakfast</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/good-ole-american-breakfast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/good-ole-american-breakfast/</guid><description>what is an american breakfast to you?
to a lot of american diner restaurants, it means pancakes, bacon, eggs, sausages, hash browns, and even sandwiches. and even among that, what kind of eggs? sausage links or sausage patties? grits or hash browns? let&amp;rsquo;s not even bother getting into the amount of things you can add to pancakes, and the varieties of breakfast sandwiches and pastries exist.
the amount of variety is endless.</description></item><item><title>any austin the video essayist</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/any-austin-the-video-essayist/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/any-austin-the-video-essayist/</guid><description>have you ever heard of any austin?
he&amp;rsquo;s a youtube video essayist who makes commenataries on video games about things that are outstandingly mundane, like power lines in GTA 5, hydrology, and unemployment surveys.
i&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by his content. his cadence and pacing, especially, is uniquely captivating in its presentation. i&amp;rsquo;ve since exhausted his catalog of skyrim related videos, and found other skyrim video essayists EXTREMELY wanting.
something about them is just too nerdy to follow.</description></item><item><title>and yet over and over</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/and-yet-over-and-over/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/and-yet-over-and-over/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;m pretty bad with my sleep schedule.
i think i&amp;rsquo;ve written about this one before but it bears repeating because it is so pervasive of a problem for me.
how do you reconcile staying up because the rest of the world is up playing games and having fun with needing to be up the next day?
at some point, something has to give. i wonder when that time will come for me.</description></item><item><title>up and down</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/up-and-down/</guid><description>the cyclical nature of life can be amusing.
which sounds extremely unemployed, but despite everything, i am actually still employed.
the amusing part of it is how right now i&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure i&amp;rsquo;m in a downturn, and yet
i have a good feeling that things will turn around pretty soon..
not for any reason that should be considered ominous. it&amp;rsquo;s just hope.
when i first began doing things that were new to me,</description></item><item><title>being honest with yourself</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/being-honest-with-yourself/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/being-honest-with-yourself/</guid><description>there comes a time when you start realizing
just how many lies you tell yourself.
stuff like assumptions about way things work,
ways you think people interpret what you do,
ways you think things should go, and ways
you do the things you do.
one i&amp;rsquo;m recently trying to tackle is my perception
of the difficulty of &amp;ldquo;doing&amp;rdquo; things.
people say stuff like, going to the gym is &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo;.
but what if it weren&amp;rsquo;t hard?</description></item><item><title>my current favorite hoodie</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/my-current-favorite-hoodie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/my-current-favorite-hoodie/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;m a big hoodie enjoyer.
i have a huge collection in my closet,
and it is my preferred top layer.
the usual issues i have with finding &amp;ldquo;good hoodies&amp;rdquo;
are that they need to meet certain criteria, namely:
a boxy silhouette (my chest is wide) slightly cropped, but not too cropped (my torso is short) arms that are nice and baggy but NOT too long (something that has a cuff that sits halfway on your hand is super ideal for the cozy vibe) a nice, structured hood that is big enough for my big ass head a heavy enough weight to conquer any morning when i feel like absolute garbage about the way i look a big enough kangaroo pouch/pockets to rest my hands in comfortably for a while, i was rocking Abercrombie&amp;rsquo;s relaxed popover hoodies.</description></item></channel></rss>