<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>pets have regen properties</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/pets-have-regen-properties/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/pets-have-regen-properties/</guid><description>when the chips are down, a cat can change it all.
i&amp;rsquo;ve been taking trips to take care of
my brother&amp;rsquo;s cat recently while he&amp;rsquo;s away.
i have to drive 30 minutes there and back (1hr total),
so it&amp;rsquo;s a little annoying when i&amp;rsquo;m on the way there,
thinking about how i have -1hr minimum in my day.
but then, i see the cat.
sweetie on the countertop.</description></item><item><title>notepad gripes</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/notepad-gripes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/notepad-gripes/</guid><description>i got some gripes with notepad.
specifically, notepad on windows 11.
to start, one thing that&amp;rsquo;s good is that it supports dark mode.
i don&amp;rsquo;t know if that was there in windows 10.
if it was, i was not appreciative enough of it to acknowledge it.
i use notepad to write these blogposts (editing .md files),
and for some god-forsaken reason, closing the notepad window
does not close the files that have been opened by notepad.</description></item><item><title>sonny boy</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/sonny-boy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/sonny-boy/</guid><description>one of my favorite anime of all time is &amp;ldquo;Sonny Boy&amp;rdquo;.
sonny boy is about a class of middle schoolers,
focused on a boy named Nagara.
as they approach the end of their middle school days,
they are suddenly transported into an alternate dimension
where the laws of the world are as fickle as they are mysterious.
nagara, mizuho, and kamabiko, from Sonny Boy.</description></item><item><title>learning experiences</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-experiences/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-experiences/</guid><description>sometimes, you just gotta take it on the chin.
a lesson i&amp;rsquo;ve had to learn many times in life is that
things aren&amp;rsquo;t always going to go as planned.
and when they don&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s important to persevere.
on the same side of that coin,
it is important to interpret your losses not strictly as negative,
but as learning experiences and as things you can learn from.
your losses become way more productive once you can do this.</description></item><item><title>happy birthdays</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/happy-birthdays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/happy-birthdays/</guid><description>happy birthday!
on the off chance the day you&amp;rsquo;re reading this is your birthday,
i will be cosmically popping off over my (and your) luck.
today, august 7th, is my birthday.
birthdays are fun, of course. in the ideal world.
you get to spend time with people you love having good food.
but i think birthdays are, due to their emotional amplitude,
also a time with the capacity for great sadness.</description></item><item><title>console gaming</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/console-gaming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/console-gaming/</guid><description>are you a console gamer?
for a while i would have random thoughts of
being someone who plays games on a console
in addition to playing PC games.
just seemed like a good mix. like a healthy balance.
&amp;ldquo;i can do console exclusives AND play PC games with friends.
win win situation! aside from buying the console.&amp;rdquo;
i wanted to grab a PS5 when they came out but
obviously supply chain issues stepped in</description></item><item><title>water bugs?</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/water-bugs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/water-bugs/</guid><description>ever heard of water bugs?
i think that&amp;rsquo;s what they&amp;rsquo;re called anyway.
they look kind of like smaller cockroaches.
we&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with them recently in the kitchen,
and my dad is one of those guys who thinks he can solve anything,
so he&amp;rsquo;s been trying strategies to defeat the water bugs.
this includes stuff like placing traps in corners,
and spraying stuff down,
and moving food so the bugs can&amp;rsquo;t get to it.</description></item><item><title>ikea is good enough for me</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/ikea-is-good-enough-for-me/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/ikea-is-good-enough-for-me/</guid><description>i like ikea quite a bit.
if you&amp;rsquo;ve somehow gotten to this page and aren&amp;rsquo;t aware of what ikea is,
ikea is a Swedish furniture store that sells modular listings for fair prices.
their quality is the definition of middle-of-the-road, and is usually just good enough.
i think it&amp;rsquo;s a common opinion that using ikea for furniture
is somewhat of settling for shittier furniture that&amp;rsquo;s easier.
it&amp;rsquo;s like ordering something off amazon instead of from an actual website.</description></item><item><title>you got games on your phone?</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/you-got-games-on-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/you-got-games-on-your-phone/</guid><description>you got games on your phone?
i know a few people who are actually really into mobile gaming.
and i mean gacha games, mainly HoYoVerse. they seem to be pretty popular.
i tried genshin out a few times and the music is actually quite relaxing.
but i could never get into the &amp;ldquo;playing it daily&amp;rdquo; part of it.
it seemed like a huge chore and not enjoyable for me.
i thought this was a reflection at one point in time</description></item><item><title>now listening to</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/now-listening-to/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/now-listening-to/</guid><description>what kind of music do you listen to?
right now i&amp;rsquo;m bumping a city pop playlist.
city pop is a term for Japanese pop music from the 80s
that usually takes a soft-rock/boogie vibe with nice funk vocals.
otherwise i have some songs in a loose playlist that are just
fun to sing in the car or are catchy to me in this moment.
i can&amp;rsquo;t tell if i&amp;rsquo;m good or bad at making playlists for the ages,</description></item><item><title>fast times at ridgemont high</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/fast-times-at-ridgemont-high/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/fast-times-at-ridgemont-high/</guid><description>you ever seen &amp;ldquo;Fast Times at Ridgemont High&amp;rdquo;?
it&amp;rsquo;s a classic coming-of-age movie that came out in 1982,
and follows the story of a bunch of kids in a year in high school,
going through life as high schoolers do.
there&amp;rsquo;s Jeff Spicoli, and his stoner shenanigans versus Mr. Hand, Brad Hamilton and his work woes, Mark Ratner and his dreams of getting a girlfriend, and the &amp;ldquo;cool&amp;rdquo; Mike Damone who grifts tickets for random people.</description></item><item><title>cloud strife</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/cloud-strife/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/cloud-strife/</guid><description>cloud strife is so cool.
i&amp;rsquo;ve been continuing my playthrough of ff7 remake recently because there&amp;rsquo;s a final fantasy 7 rebirth concert happening in Chicago that i&amp;rsquo;m scheduled to go to, and considering i haven&amp;rsquo;t.. played through ff7 rebirth yet.. i figured it was time to get my ass in gear. the concert is in three weeks, and i was about halfway through remake at the time of realizing i needed to get my act together.</description></item><item><title>deleting old files</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/deleting-old-files/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/deleting-old-files/</guid><description>how good are you at letting go?
as i was using my rental Fujifilm x-t30ii,
i had to learn more about good storage hygiene for my SD card.
those RAW files are huge! (like 60mb each!)
after each day of shooting when i would get to editing in lightroom,
i would stage photos for editing and throw away the rest.
but throwing away the photos felt.. a little difficult.
i&amp;rsquo;m the kind of person who likes keeping things around</description></item><item><title>amazon prime</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/amazon-prime/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/amazon-prime/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve had an amazon prime subscription since 2018,
and i use amazon to buy so many things.
basically anything i don&amp;rsquo;t care to go buy in-person,
potentially spending some of my afternoon going out to buy things,
i would rather buy on amazon with prime.
it&amp;rsquo;s super convenient.
but i know it comes at a cost to the universe.
sometimes that thought wins,
the thought of the environment suffering indirectly</description></item><item><title>going places on your own</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/going-places-on-your-own/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/going-places-on-your-own/</guid><description>do you ever go somewhere to eat on your own?
it feels a little weird, right?
we&amp;rsquo;re very used to going with at least one other person,
or at least i do that a lot of the time.
i recently went to mitsuwa in Arlington Heights
to get some pictures on my rental Fujifilm X-T30II.
&amp;ldquo;the red lanterns of tokyo shokudo, in the food court.</description></item><item><title>lowballing people on facebook marketplace</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/lowballing-people-on-facebook-marketplace/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/lowballing-people-on-facebook-marketplace/</guid><description>you ever go on facebook marketplace and lowball people?
this is some of the funniest shit ever, i think.
a lot of funny things are based in suffering, either your own
or other peoples' (inflicted either by you or by the universe.)
i&amp;rsquo;m in the market for a PS5 and i have a buddy on the lookout,
but in the meantime i&amp;rsquo;m also checking facebook marketplace,
and brother am i lowballing.</description></item><item><title>photowalk in the neighborhood</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/photowalk-in-the-neighborhood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/photowalk-in-the-neighborhood/</guid><description>today, i went on a photowalk with the Fujifilm X-T30ii i rented for a week.
i walked around my neighborhood and had a great time!
here&amp;rsquo;s some pictures. enjoy!
&amp;ldquo;taking a break.&amp;quot; &amp;ldquo;anyone wanna do a game of pick-up?&amp;quot; &amp;ldquo;phew, glad i&amp;rsquo;m not out there.</description></item><item><title>random bouts of rage</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/random-bouts-of-rage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/random-bouts-of-rage/</guid><description>i think many men (not women) on this planet are primarily characterized by one of two emotions. you&amp;rsquo;re either anger based or horny based. that is to say, what emotion do people use to power their actions most commonly? for the purposes of this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on the prior.
when you&amp;rsquo;re a kid growing up, it&amp;rsquo;s natural to seek the approval of your peers. it&amp;rsquo;s a fundamental social skill that we carry as adults, and satiating this social hunger is, perhaps not surprisingly, a natural wrapper around many actions we perform.</description></item><item><title>doing laundry</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/doing-laundry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/doing-laundry/</guid><description>what do you think of doing laundry?
i know some people who can&amp;rsquo;t stand laundry,
and they need their s/o or somebody else to do it for them,
or they will otherwise do it with great mental stress.
for me, laundry is kind of relaxing.
it&amp;rsquo;s nice to set things and forget them,
come back later,
and see that they&amp;rsquo;ve made progress.
laundry day for my parents.</description></item><item><title>making purchases worth it</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/making-purchases-worth-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/making-purchases-worth-it/</guid><description>how easy is it for you to say it was &amp;ldquo;worth it&amp;rdquo; when you buy something?
do you spend your money on things that have dubious practicality,
or otherwise applicability in your life?
i&amp;rsquo;m going through a pretty heavy mirrorless camera research phase..
if this sounds interesting, please look forward to the results!
but to the point, i rented a Fujifilm X-T30II for the duration of 7 days,
and almost convinced myself to buy the X-T50 before the X-T30II had even arrived!</description></item><item><title>lotion and preventative mindsets</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/lotion-and-preventative-mindsets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/lotion-and-preventative-mindsets/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve never had a &amp;ldquo;perfect&amp;rdquo; skincare routine.
in fact, i don&amp;rsquo;t even know what that would look like,
aside from the God of Skincare telling me &amp;ldquo;Yep, that&amp;rsquo;s it. You&amp;rsquo;re doing everything right.&amp;rdquo;
i keep it pretty simple,
just Cetaphil lotion (i tried cerave, my skin likes Cetaphil more)
and daily facial cleansing.
but i&amp;rsquo;ve had my fair share of back acne issues
as a result of my proclivity to perspiration.</description></item><item><title>how to unlock shadow the hedgehog in ssbb</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/how-to-unlock-shadow-the-hedgehog-in-ssbb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/how-to-unlock-shadow-the-hedgehog-in-ssbb/</guid><description>do you remember those stupid videos
where people would be like &amp;ldquo;how to unlock shadow in smash bros&amp;rdquo;
and it would say you had to do multi-man smash on hard
for like 20 minutes without losing a single stock or some dumb shit
and people fell for it?
i just randomly remembered those videos today.
the internet was such a different time. i miss it.
it&amp;rsquo;s only natural to miss it.</description></item><item><title>boba milk tea</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/boba-milk-tea/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/boba-milk-tea/</guid><description>do you like drinking boba milk tea?
or just milk tea in general?
milk tea is in a weird spot for me as this thing that somehow people view as far more socially acceptable to drink than other similar sweet drinks that are probably outright considered desserts instead of whatever half-category milk teas have carved out for themselves, and it&amp;rsquo;s just interesting to me how far the words &amp;ldquo;milk&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;tea&amp;rdquo; go to carry the elusive nature of their nutrition.</description></item><item><title>the every day</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-every-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-every-day/</guid><description>when you think of everyday things, what do you think of?
do you think of people? or of sounds? or of feelings? or of sights?
a familiar sight is my mom&amp;rsquo;s teacup, usually found sitting on the dining table or the living room table.
(and occasionally the kitchen countertop when she forgets to bring it upstairs.)
my mom&amp;rsquo;s preferred mug. usually contains green tea.</description></item><item><title>korean bbq is wonderful</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/korean-bbq-is-wonderful/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/korean-bbq-is-wonderful/</guid><description>have you ever been to a korean bbq place before?
i love going with my friends to Mr. Kimchi in Mt. Prospect.
we don&amp;rsquo;t go particularly often, but when we do, i always enjoy myself.
my friends and i at a booth in mr. kimchi, taken on my minolta x-570. korean bbq is where you sit down at a table that has a grill in the center,</description></item><item><title>salmon and rice (and eggs)</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/salmon-and-rice-and-eggs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/salmon-and-rice-and-eggs/</guid><description>a classic dish i had when i was in college was salmon and rice.
today, i&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing with you the recipe, that you may also enjoy it.
you will need the following:
Salmon (i got mine from Costco) White rice Knorr Tamarind Soup Mix or Sinigang na Sampalok Mix Olive oil Salt Pepper Two eggs (optional) Unsalted butter (optional) Cream cheese (optional) begin with as many pieces of salmon as you like.</description></item><item><title>pictures and photography 2</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/pictures-and-photography-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/pictures-and-photography-2/</guid><description>remember how last time i talked about photography
i mentioned i may one day get a camera of my own?
well, it happened.
sanukiseimen udon, at mitsuwa arlington heights. i got a minolta x-570, a camera made in 1983
as a low-cost alternative to the x-700.
it is revered for its strictly manual capabilities
and its good-for-its-time functioning lightmeter.</description></item><item><title>visual and auditory cues</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/visual-and-auditory-cues/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/visual-and-auditory-cues/</guid><description>have you ever felt compelled to do something
strictly off of an audio or visual cue?
it&amp;rsquo;s interesting how pavlovian conditioning still holds up
to this day, for mammals as advanced as humans are.
using cues like these can help you build habits
like remembering to brush your teeth, or to drink water.
in my case, however, it&amp;rsquo;s a bit annoying.
it seems at some point i formed an visual/auditory cue</description></item><item><title>tagalog is an onomatopoeic language</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/tagalog-is-an-onomatopoeic-language/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/tagalog-is-an-onomatopoeic-language/</guid><description>tagalog is a fascinatingly onomatopoeic language.
to be onomatopoeic in this sense means that often
the words in this language are sonically descriptive
of what their definitions are.
for example: &amp;ldquo;kulimlim&amp;rdquo; is a word that means &amp;ldquo;cloudy&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;gloomy&amp;rdquo;.
and &amp;ldquo;bangga&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;collision&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;crash&amp;rdquo;, as in a car crash.
or &amp;ldquo;masaya&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;very happy&amp;rdquo;, and as you say the word &amp;ldquo;masaya&amp;rdquo;,
you may notice your mouth naturally opens to a smile.</description></item><item><title>breathing fresh air</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/breathing-fresh-air/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/breathing-fresh-air/</guid><description>never underestimate the power of some fresh air.
in general, taking a breather is a super good strategy
for tackling problems in the most effective way.
i&amp;rsquo;m sure this isn&amp;rsquo;t the first time you&amp;rsquo;ve heard this advice.
but this certainly does not need to be the last time you hear it, either.
but specifically breathing air from a different place
than the one you&amp;rsquo;re currently in hits so massively differently.</description></item><item><title>napping can be dangerous</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/napping-can-be-dangerous/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/napping-can-be-dangerous/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve been engaging in naps recently..
i try not to nap whenever i can muster the willpower for it,
but with all these nights of playing final fantasy xiv,
i get up in the mornings and i&amp;rsquo;m like &amp;ldquo;fuuuhuuuck.&amp;rdquo;
and so, taking a nap after my mandatory morning meetings?
fucking hits like no other. so satisfying. it&amp;rsquo;s amazing.
and it&amp;rsquo;s goddamn dangerous.
i&amp;rsquo;m of the belief that biological reinforcement is a powerful</description></item><item><title>staying hydrated</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/staying-hydrated/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/staying-hydrated/</guid><description>i don&amp;rsquo;t know about you guys,
but i&amp;rsquo;m not the best at staying hydrated.
sometimes i&amp;rsquo;ll get a dull headache and think,
&amp;ldquo;man this sucks. why is this happening?&amp;rdquo;
then i remember it&amp;rsquo;s been, oh, i don&amp;rsquo;t know,
four hours since i last drank water.
water needs no introduction. it&amp;rsquo;s the goat liquid.
they talk about getting a minimum amount of water per day,
but i&amp;rsquo;m pretty bad at tracking how much water i&amp;rsquo;ve drank.</description></item><item><title>haircuts are great</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/haircuts-are-great/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/haircuts-are-great/</guid><description>i love the feeling of having a fresh haircut.
all those days or weeks of building up to getting one,
and the anticipation of when you feel it&amp;rsquo;s just right to get one
is finally released.
for my asian hair, when it gets too long (for my liking)
it grows outwards pretty obtusely on the back and sides.
so i prefer having a taper fade of some kind to keep those sides short.</description></item><item><title>rainy days</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/rainy-days/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/rainy-days/</guid><description>how do you feel about rainy days?
i like rainy days a lot.
they enhance some kind of metaphysical coziness about the air.
and although it&amp;rsquo;s humid and a bit sticky at times,
the atmosphere sure makes for a good opportunity
to have a nice hot bowl of ramen noodles!
between driving in the rain, seeing the drops falling on your car,
or staying at home in the rain, hearing it land on your rooftop,</description></item><item><title>the mondays</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-mondays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-mondays/</guid><description>does anyone like mondays?
i mean aside from like, david goggins i guess.
he probably also doesn&amp;rsquo;t like mondays but he like..
uses the fuel of people hating mondays to do MORE shit on mondays.
mondays are a complete struggle for me, as they are for many.
switching gears from weekend gaming (or other social activities)
back to work and how to get stuff done at work,
on top of figuring out where the hell you were last week.</description></item><item><title>shared suffering</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/shared-suffering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/shared-suffering/</guid><description>one of my favorite concepts ever has to be shared suffering.
when groups of people go through the same slog of bullshit,
and they all know amongst themselves that none of them are enjoying it,
but they gotta do it because it&amp;rsquo;s a requirement for something else.
as you could have probably guessed by now,
my primary example is from final fantasy xiv.
in it, there was once this grueling slog of a set of dungeons</description></item><item><title>ordering food</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/ordering-food/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/ordering-food/</guid><description>are you the kind of person where when you eat out,
you always order the same thing from the same place?
i tend to do this a lot.
for example, my chipotle order is a:
bowl steak &amp;amp; fajitas white rice no beans queso corn mild salsa on occasion i&amp;rsquo;ll turn this into a burrito, but for the most part,
this is what gets the job done for me.</description></item><item><title>attention and hunger</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/attention-and-hunger/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/attention-and-hunger/</guid><description>do you ever lose your sense of hunger when focused?
i think it&amp;rsquo;s super interesting that this happens.
dr. k spoke about this once in the lens of ayurvedic teaching.
something along the lines of your attention being a limited resource,
like you have 100 attention points to spend on any amount of things at a time.
so if you manage to focus so intently on one thing,
you actually minimize the capacity to have your attention grabbed</description></item><item><title>changing things up</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/changing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/changing-things-up/</guid><description>do you ever find it interesting how we feel the need to change things up every now and then?
as humans, we crave the new and get bored of the old..
such ingratitude. after all the times the old has saved our lives!
like when we brush our teeth! or remember to take our meds!
it could be a superpower in its own right to never get bored of something, couldn&amp;rsquo;t it?</description></item><item><title>priorities or otherwise</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/priorities-or-otherwise/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/priorities-or-otherwise/</guid><description>when i have problems justifying my current choices,
i remember words a wise man once told me:
There&amp;rsquo;s no such thing as &amp;ldquo;not having the time.&amp;quot;
There are only priorities, and where they are placed.
-S.S., 2024
although the quote is likely stolen from a source of his own,
the moments i spend pondering this idea are comforting.
indeed, his point is that when we tell ourselves we&amp;rsquo;d like to do something,</description></item><item><title>the realforce r2 keyboard</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-realforce-r2-keyboard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-realforce-r2-keyboard/</guid><description>the current keyboard i use is the Realforce R2 Tenkeyless in the ivory colorway.
in the beginning of my keyboard journey, i started with a Leopold FC750R.
also a tenkeyless, but with mechanical switches instead of Topre switches.
i originally purchased it after hearing about the Leopold FC660C,
and being confused as to why it was so expensive,
but still wanting the Leopold name behind my typing instrument of choice.</description></item><item><title>waiting in line</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/waiting-in-line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/waiting-in-line/</guid><description>waiting in line is a divisive topic in my experience.
some people can&amp;rsquo;t tolerate it at all, while others look forward to making use of their time while waiting.
i knew a guy once who told me traffic was the most insufferable thing he had to deal with on a regular basis.
which is fair to him, i think his commute was something like 35-45 minutes every day back and forth.</description></item><item><title>the end of the day</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-end-of-the-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-end-of-the-day/</guid><description>what&amp;rsquo;s your ideal end to the day like?
one that&amp;rsquo;s particularly hard for me to beat
is taking a good dump after a long day of eating good food.
which might sound crass, but hear me out; it&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate relief.
after travelling and seeing the sights with your friends and walking around,
talking and eating food at restaurants you&amp;rsquo;ve never been to before,
you end up back in the comfort of your own home, your intestines churning.</description></item><item><title>being an npc</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/being-an-npc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/being-an-npc/</guid><description>i was thinking today about what it&amp;rsquo;s like being an npc.
in the figurative sense of being an npc with reference to other people,
and literally being an npc in like a video game or a movie or something.
like in a scene where the main character overhears something important
while they&amp;rsquo;re at a bar because two dudes are having a conversation that&amp;rsquo;s
just a little too loud, i&amp;rsquo;m imagining those guys getting interviewing like it&amp;rsquo;s</description></item><item><title>talking to yourself in traffic</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-yourself-in-traffic/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-yourself-in-traffic/</guid><description>do you ever talk to yourself? i recommend it. it can be quite fun.
some of the greatest laughs i&amp;rsquo;ve ever had were from jokes i said while talking to myself.
i was talking to myself earlier today when i was driving home from a bakery.
the car in front of me was going amazingly slowly,
but we were at that vague distance from where i would left turn that it&amp;rsquo;s like,</description></item><item><title>sounds and being weird</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/sounds-and-being-weird/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/sounds-and-being-weird/</guid><description>anyone else listen to stuff that only they listen to, and none of your friends can relate?
there&amp;rsquo;s a few things i&amp;rsquo;ve found that basically only i know myself to listen to:
ambient sound videos (walking in tokyo, library study asmr, sounds of a mcdonald&amp;rsquo;s) animal crossing music for fun (i downloaded local versions to listen to on spotify) the same thing that isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily a full song for an obscenely long time once when grinding uni work, i listened to Dark Fantasy by Kanye West but just the first part where they literally go &amp;ldquo;can we get much higher so high oh oh oh&amp;rdquo; for 30 minutes straight work/study jazz streams on youtube that kind of don&amp;rsquo;t even feel like real music my coworkers and i were going to lunch one day and i was the driver,</description></item><item><title>my coffee journey</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/my-coffee-journey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/my-coffee-journey/</guid><description>last year in January, i decided that i needed an addiction.
a new one, not just the usual childish addictions like videogames and anime.
no, i needed an adult addiction that was so powerful that it carries with it
an air of haughtiness that blows away all who dare question its validity.
so i decided to get into coffee.
i decided to get into making pour-over coffee at home for a few reasons:</description></item><item><title>final fantasy xiv</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/final-fantasy-xiv/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/final-fantasy-xiv/</guid><description>i used to play a lot of final fantasy xiv, the MMORPG of the final fantasy series.
i got into it back in 2020 when my senior at UIUC, jared, invited me to play with him.
he was trying to rope as many people as he possibly could into the game
because, unsurprisingly, MMOs are a lot more fun with good friends to play with.
i humored him on the idea because in my childhood and elementary school years,</description></item><item><title>pictures and photography</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/pictures-and-photography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/pictures-and-photography/</guid><description>we all go on random youtube binges right?
the ones where it&amp;rsquo;s a topic that you&amp;rsquo;ve briefly touched in the past,
and you never got fully into but seemed interesting at the time.
one of those for me is professional photography.
as someone who has done a fairly minimal amount of research into the
more detailed parts of the workflow of it all,
f numbers, apertures, shooting speeds, lens sizes, digital and film,</description></item><item><title>talking to people</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/talking-to-people/</guid><description>how do you feel about being at parties with strangers?
do you go into it thinking it&amp;rsquo;s an exciting chance to meet new people?
are you anxious about having to answer questions about who you are?
every time i&amp;rsquo;m put in that situation, i wonder why i tend more to anxiety
rather than curiosity.
was it easier that way at some point in time? &amp;hellip;easier for who?
it&amp;rsquo;s quite relatable, actually.</description></item><item><title>thinking and doing</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/thinking-and-doing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/thinking-and-doing/</guid><description>thinking and doing are two modes of operation that i consider when talking about work.
this is to say i choose not to apply it with something whimsical or less &amp;ldquo;important&amp;rdquo;,
like my attitude with cooking eggs, or how i decide what clothes to wear.
&amp;ldquo;thinking&amp;rdquo; is when you make a plan of action to do something.
i think about it most when doing work at my job,
because usually to do my job, i need to at least plan a little bit.</description></item><item><title>mashing</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/mashing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/mashing/</guid><description>if you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with what &amp;ldquo;mashing&amp;rdquo; is, i&amp;rsquo;ll try to explain.
&amp;ldquo;mashing&amp;rdquo; is when there is a logical way to reach a solution,
but instead of going on that path,
you guess a solution until you either give up or it miraculously works.
in the context of fighting games, when you get knocked down to the ground,
you have to respond to a multitude of possible attacks from the opponent:</description></item><item><title>learning the ropes</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-the-ropes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/learning-the-ropes/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;learning the ropes&amp;rdquo; is very much mentally associated in my brain with &amp;ldquo;day 2&amp;rdquo;. why? in swords and sandals II: emperor&amp;rsquo;s reign, every day has a title associated with it. day 1 is &amp;ldquo;glorious freedom&amp;rdquo;. day 2 is &amp;ldquo;learning the ropes.&amp;rdquo; so, this is today&amp;rsquo;s title.
i mentioned last time that i wanted to at least roughly jot down the steps it took to get this webserver up and running, so i&amp;rsquo;ll use this time to recall them.</description></item><item><title>space pilot 3000</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/space-pilot-3000/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/space-pilot-3000/</guid><description>the title of today&amp;rsquo;s post, the very first one, is from futurama, a show about an average dude named Fry who gets cryogenically frozen in the year 2000 and wakes up in the year 3000 to earth being an interstellar civilization. following his job as a pizza delivery boy in the past, he becomes a spaceship delivery boy in the future, hence the name &amp;ldquo;space pilot 3000&amp;rdquo;. i always liked the name, it just sounds neat.</description></item></channel></rss>