<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>changing seasons</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/changing-seasons/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/changing-seasons/</guid><description>when September rolls around is when i start thinking that seasons are changing.
persona 3 has a great track called changing of the seasons that i think of this time of year (although in-game, this track doesn&amp;rsquo;t play around September.)
my 2nd favorite season is probably fall, next to winter. the red and orange colored leaves are just amazing to look at. makes you feel young when you drive underneath trees like that.</description></item><item><title>saturday nights</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/saturday-nights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/saturday-nights/</guid><description>it&amp;rsquo;s saturday night.
the boys are in discord, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to game.
what ensues is a tale of camaraderie, triumph, loss, despair, battle,
but ultimately, through it all, the best vibes of all time.
i invite you to listen to saturday nights by inoha,
in the commemoration of awesome saturday nights.
we don&amp;rsquo;t have that many, people!
thanks for reading today&amp;rsquo;s post.
let&amp;rsquo;s get it started.</description></item><item><title>monthly calendars</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/monthly-calendars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/monthly-calendars/</guid><description>i used to not have any physical calendars because i felt i wasn&amp;rsquo;t organized enough to make use of a calendar.
then, at some point, i decided some calendars just look quite neat and they offer value on their own by acting as nice decoration.
helenpeanut&amp;rsquo;s 2024 calendar featuring Haikyuu!! characters. i have this one by helenpeanut featuring Haikyuu!! characters, which is an anime about highschoolers in Japan playing volleyball and trying to be the best in the country.</description></item><item><title>touching grass</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/touching-grass/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/touching-grass/</guid><description>have you ever been told to &amp;ldquo;touch grass&amp;rdquo;?
&amp;ldquo;touching grass&amp;rdquo; is a term used on the internet to tell people
that they need to go outside and re-align themselves with reality,
because their behavior on the internet is so outlandish and unreasonable
that it surely implies they haven&amp;rsquo;t spoken to a real human in some time.
&amp;ldquo;touching grass&amp;rdquo;, therefore, is something you can only do outside.
and with your real body, not a virtual one.</description></item><item><title>logic's new album</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/logics-new-album/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/logics-new-album/</guid><description>when i was in high school, i used to listen to Logic.
(and also for a bit in college)
my two favorite albums of his were Under Pressure and The Incredible True Story,
his freshman and sophomore albums that hearken me back to the days
of driving my friends to off-campus lunch in high school, bumping &amp;ldquo;Stainless&amp;rdquo; in the car.
after he released the Everybody album to divisive reviews,
he underwent an extremely corny arc where all his music just&amp;hellip; wasn&amp;rsquo;t hitting the same.</description></item><item><title>deadlock and dota 2</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/deadlock-and-dota-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/deadlock-and-dota-2/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve recently been playing valve&amp;rsquo;s unreleased hero shooter, Deadlock.
my background is that i played a decent (400-600hrs) amount of overwatch/overwatch 2,
and a pretty good amount (~2000hrs) of Dota 2, Valve&amp;rsquo;s flagship MOBA.
i&amp;rsquo;m enjoying the game a lot! some of the visuals in-game are a little
rough around the edges, but for the most part, i like the aesthetic they&amp;rsquo;re going for.
i believe the name of the map is the Rotten Apple, in a kind of 50&amp;rsquo;s NYC vibe.</description></item><item><title>where i'm at with reading right now</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/where-im-at-with-reading-right-now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/where-im-at-with-reading-right-now/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;m on the 2nd to last chapter of Blood, Sweat, and Pixels by Jason Schreier, videogame journalist. i got to this point a week or so ago, and i was thinking &amp;ldquo;man, maybe i should just sit down and finish this book. there&amp;rsquo;s only two chapters left!&amp;rdquo;
but this year i&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking more about the reading process, and reading to have read rather than trying to really sit with a book.</description></item></channel></rss>