<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>orchestra concerts</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/orchestra-concerts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/orchestra-concerts/</guid><description>you ever go to a symphony orchestra concert?
as a final fantasy fan, i&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to go
to a few &amp;ldquo;Distant Worlds&amp;rdquo; performances at the
Chicago Symphony Center on Michigan Avenue.
today, i went to see the FF7 Rebirth Symphony Orchestra
on their second date of their worldwide tour!
i had the pleasure of going with a couple of friends.
my view from the balcony.</description></item><item><title>odd obsessions</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/odd-obsessions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/odd-obsessions/</guid><description>odd obsessions are one of the easiest ways to get to know someone.
i&amp;rsquo;ve talked about talking to people before,
where my point was that we should be understanding that
the basis of many relationships can be around mundane things.
but when you and another person are both into a niche thing?
that&amp;rsquo;s when the magic happens, i think.
it depends on how weird it is, of course.
having an NBA buddy and having a stamp collection buddy;</description></item><item><title>taking it easy</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/taking-it-easy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/taking-it-easy/</guid><description>are you easy-going? or are you a gas-gas-gas type?
nowadays more than ever,
it&amp;rsquo;s hard to convince yourself to take things easy.
we live in a culture of go-getters and efficiency.
i believe in the ebb and flow of life&amp;rsquo;s rhythm,
and in the idea of equivalent exchange.
good times simply must follow bad ones.
so when i recognize that times are tough,
and effort must be exerted to see success,</description></item><item><title>home-cooked meals</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/home-cooked-meals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/home-cooked-meals/</guid><description>home-cooked meals are just the best, right?
at this point in my life, i live at home
and enjoy the benefits of, for most meals,
being able to eat home-cooked meals from my parents.
for a while i&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to get more into
cooking regularly, but there are some issues i have
with cooking in this particular home:
storage issues with existing items making food for more than one person trying recipes with ingredients that probably won&amp;rsquo;t be used frequently not to mention the natural struggle of needing to</description></item><item><title>today's photowalk</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/todays-photowalk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/todays-photowalk/</guid><description>today i went on a walk on the grounds near my workplace and took photos.
i&amp;rsquo;d like to share a few here. take a look!
An Airgas liquid nitrogen tank. shot with fuji x-t50. a fleet of trucks. shot with fuji x-t50. i love trees with sky backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>in spite of logic</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-spite-of-logic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-spite-of-logic/</guid><description>you ever do something you know you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be doing?
i&amp;rsquo;m currently playing through Final Fantasy VII Rebirth,
a game with over a hundred hours of content inside,
but also holding the capability to be finished in under 30 hours.
my reason for playing this game is because i have a concert
for the FFVII Rebirth Orchestra this saturday the 17th
wherein spoilers for the game will be shown.
therefore, i need to complete the game as fast as possible</description></item><item><title>pets have regen properties</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/pets-have-regen-properties/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/pets-have-regen-properties/</guid><description>when the chips are down, a cat can change it all.
i&amp;rsquo;ve been taking trips to take care of
my brother&amp;rsquo;s cat recently while he&amp;rsquo;s away.
i have to drive 30 minutes there and back (1hr total),
so it&amp;rsquo;s a little annoying when i&amp;rsquo;m on the way there,
thinking about how i have -1hr minimum in my day.
but then, i see the cat.
sweetie on the countertop.</description></item></channel></rss>