<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the initial obstacle</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-initial-obstacle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-initial-obstacle/</guid><description>we&amp;rsquo;re all familiar with how hard it is to start.
it&amp;rsquo;s always the first step, it only gets easier,
etc, etc. platitudes and cliches, all about the
difficulty of doing something new in starting
from zero and just, really, truly doing it.
i am reminded of this on this day, and so
i wanted to share it with you, the gooberverse.
that we may all find freedom in trying something new.</description></item><item><title>exceedingly spicy food</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/exceedingly-spicy-food/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/exceedingly-spicy-food/</guid><description>how are you with your spices?
when i was a teenager i would fuck heavy with
getting super spicy flavored stuff and getting
things that were spicy just thinking it would be
&amp;ldquo;tastier&amp;rdquo; than mild alternatives, somehow.
could be anything from chip flavors,
to chicken wings and their sauces,
to bowls of ramen noodles:
if i could get spicy, i probably would.
as i&amp;rsquo;ve grown, and successfully having destroyed
my stomach and intestinal lining,</description></item><item><title>when covid happened</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/when-covid-happened/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/when-covid-happened/</guid><description>where were you when you heard the news about covid-19?
i was a sophomore in college,
hearing rumors about some new viral infection
that was rivaling the likes of influenza.
i remember being at my campus supermarket,
thinking &amp;ldquo;hmm.. i guess i don&amp;rsquo;t have any face masks.
maybe i should buy some before it gets bad..&amp;rdquo;
it was just about to be spring break, too.
i remember my parents telling me to stay at my apartment,</description></item><item><title>look back by tatsuki fujimoto</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/look-back-by-tatsuki-fujimoto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/look-back-by-tatsuki-fujimoto/</guid><description>today i saw LOOK BACK, from the creator of CHAINSAW MAN in theaters.
LOOK BACK is an animated film about two girls who aspire to be mangaka,
or manga artists. it is a movie adaptation of a one-shot from Tatsuki Fujimoto,
the creator of popular manga CHAINSAW MAN, starring Denji (the chainsaw man).
one-shots in manga are a mangaka&amp;rsquo;s way of creative expression
either between projects or without the restriction of ongoing ones.</description></item><item><title>waiting to be served at a restaurant</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/waiting-to-be-served-at-a-restaurant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/waiting-to-be-served-at-a-restaurant/</guid><description>you ever had a long wait for your food at a sit-down?
depending on the time you go, it makes sense.
lunch rush, or at a breakfast place maybe brunch rush,
the workers are gonna be busy and you won&amp;rsquo;t get it out
in like, 10 minutes. but ideally before 25 minutes, right?
i developed a new pang of self-consciousness while waiting
for my server to come take my order at a restaurant today:</description></item><item><title>the CCP</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-ccp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-ccp/</guid><description>how do you feel about CCP?
and i ain&amp;rsquo;t talking about the Chinese Communist Party,
i&amp;rsquo;m talking about Chocolate Chip Pancakes.
chocolate chip pancakes. i somewhat got into chocolate chip pancakes after
watching The Good Doctor because of all the Dr. Han memes
that were on Twitter, the show in which the protagonist,
Dr. Shaun Murphy&amp;rsquo;s favorite food is chocolate chip pancakes.</description></item><item><title>legend of zelda wind waker</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/legend-of-zelda-wind-waker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/legend-of-zelda-wind-waker/</guid><description>remember the Nintendo GameCube?
the GameCube was host to many legendary Nintendo titles,
like Super Smash Bros. Melee and Mario Kart Double Dash.
however, if you ask me what was a standout hit from that time,
i&amp;rsquo;ve gotta go with The Legend of Zelda: Wind Waker.
Link in Wind Waker, riding the King of Red Lions. in Wind Waker, you control Link as he navigates across the seas</description></item></channel></rss>