<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>by these hands the light of science</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/by-these-hands-the-light-of-science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/by-these-hands-the-light-of-science/</guid><description>the title of today&amp;rsquo;s blogpost is from a song from
the dr. stone anime soundtrack, stylized in all caps as
BY THESE HANDS, THE LIGHT OF SCIENCE.
in the beginning of dr. stone, one of the big goals of the
main characters is to invent a way of generating light
without the need for fires. thus, they invent lightbulbs
and on the way make use of electricity. ergo, the title.</description></item><item><title>in loving memory of valiaa</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-loving-memory-of-valiaa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/in-loving-memory-of-valiaa/</guid><description>i first met val doing FRU pf when i was still an ulti nooblet.
at the time, i was trying to parse better while not letting my teammates die.
i had a persecution complex that my cohealers would blame me for chadding them all the time.
i met and played with a lot of cohealers in my journey,
but val stood out to me because not only did he not accuse me of chadding him,</description></item><item><title>i miss who i was when i played maplestory</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/i-miss-who-i-was-when-i-played-maplestory/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/i-miss-who-i-was-when-i-played-maplestory/</guid><description>have you ever heard of maplestory?
the ride from ellinia to orbis via airship in maplestory. maplestory is a korean mmo by Nexon featuring 2d-sidescrolling anime
characters in a rpg fantasy setting fighting to rid the world of evil.
in nearly every sense of the word, it is quintessentially mmorpg.
although i never got into raiding when i played maplestory,</description></item><item><title>oh to be your constant companion</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/oh-to-be-your-constant-companion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/oh-to-be-your-constant-companion/</guid><description>last year i went to panama city beach in florida for a work trip.
i was there for about a week. i spent most of the daytime in a warehouse
setting things up for an optical experiment we were running,
and i spent the evenings after work hours were over doing
whatever took my fancy that day.
i tried a lot of different food places. seafood boils, crabs, ice creams,</description></item><item><title>light writing</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/light-writing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/light-writing/</guid><description>people talk about light reading. light novels. but light writing?
never heard of that in my life.
i&amp;rsquo;ll say from my perspective, it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that there are fewer writers
than there are readers. it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a normal past-time, depending on
what circles you run in, to consider actively &amp;ldquo;writing&amp;rdquo; a hobby.
much less &amp;ldquo;light writing&amp;rdquo;, which is to draw a comparison between itself and
&amp;ldquo;heavy writing&amp;rdquo;. which i guess could mean working on a book?</description></item><item><title>tomorrow</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/tomorrow/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/tomorrow/</guid><description>when you reach tomorrow, it becomes today.
isn&amp;rsquo;t it fucked up how we&amp;rsquo;ll never see tomorrow?
it&amp;rsquo;s all dependent on your frame of reference.
the buddhists say that being present and finding yourself in the present
is the key to avoiding the anxiety of the future and the grief of the past.
i&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of that ideology. we can only really do something today,
here and now. there is no tomorrow waiting for us in the sense of</description></item><item><title>some of the things i wish i could say 2</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/some-of-the-things-i-wish-i-could-say-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/some-of-the-things-i-wish-i-could-say-2/</guid><description>this post originally contained a letter i wrote to a friend that i treated poorly
who i wanted to make up with. the letter was meant to be an apology for my actions
and a statement on how i&amp;rsquo;m working on changing for the better.
out of cringe, i&amp;rsquo;m redacting it and leaving this message in its place.
thanks for reading today&amp;rsquo;s post.
i needed to do a bit of reflection it seems</description></item></channel></rss>