<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the hidden cost of transitions</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-hidden-cost-of-transitions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-hidden-cost-of-transitions/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking recently about the hidden cost of transitions between activities.
when it comes to filling your day with things that you can look back on and be satisfied with, one thing that happens regardless of activity or action is the transition between A and B. this can be anything from driving home to changing clothes to just simply mentally preparing yourself. deceptively, these moments are where the time you intend on dedicating to the actual activity can be stolen.</description></item><item><title>the beauty of online returns</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-beauty-of-online-returns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/the-beauty-of-online-returns/</guid><description>are you an online shopper?
i make a fair amount of purchases online,
be it on Amazon, or clothing stores, or hobbyist sites.
to be honest, the convenience is simply unmatched.
i think about how much time i save having to drive to the store
or having to find a physical location in general for a thing i wanna buy,
and it feels so satisfying.
granted, this feeling of satisfaction is fueled by the dire</description></item><item><title>understanding the context of your parents</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/understanding-the-context-of-your-parents/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/understanding-the-context-of-your-parents/</guid><description>many times we can be rash in our judgments.
i, like many children, argue with my parents.
we have occasional conflicts in our ideas about life.
and i have come to understand that the context of their lives
are key to reaching an understanding of my own.
that is to say, sometimes they just get pissed at me
because they need something to be pissed at.
other times, i find genuine merit behind my parents' criticisms.</description></item><item><title>hot chocolate in the summer</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/hot-chocolate-in-the-summer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/hot-chocolate-in-the-summer/</guid><description>hot chocolate in the summer is underrated.
as someone whose favorite season is winter, which is, of course
the season of hot chocolate, i often find myself reaching for a mug
of hot cocoa, especially in the summertime (since winter seems so far away..)
i&amp;rsquo;m not too snobby about my choice of hot chocolate, either.
swiss miss is the classic hot chocolate experience and i think it&amp;rsquo;s fine,
but i&amp;rsquo;ve recently been trying out Ghirardelli premium to great satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>running it down mid</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/running-it-down-mid/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/running-it-down-mid/</guid><description>if you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been in a situation where the goal is clear,
and you know with certainty what you must do to succeed,
yet you still choose to do something that&amp;rsquo;s not only
NOT what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to do, but even the exact OPPOSITE
of what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to be doing,
you have &amp;ldquo;ran it down.&amp;rdquo;
running it down mid is a term that comes from MOBAs
like League of Legends and Dota 2, where there&amp;rsquo;s</description></item><item><title>awolnation wasn't the worst</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/awolnation-wasnt-the-worst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/awolnation-wasnt-the-worst/</guid><description>i don&amp;rsquo;t know what public opinion is on awolnation,
but i&amp;rsquo;d like to say i actually like their music.
undoubtedly their most famous track is &amp;ldquo;Sail&amp;rdquo; which terrorized
the internet and memes for the better part of a year around 2011.
following their success with &amp;ldquo;Sail&amp;rdquo;, they received deals from Valve
to make music packs for some of their games, like CS:GO and Dota 2.
in 2018, they released &amp;ldquo;Here Come the Runts&amp;rdquo;, which featured</description></item><item><title>ramen noodles as a meal</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/ramen-noodles-as-a-meal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/ramen-noodles-as-a-meal/</guid><description>do you enjoy eating ramen noodles?
i think part of me romanticizes ramen noodles
because of their association with anime and japan.
ichiraku ramen from Naruto just made it look so delicious.
kyuramen x tbaar wall art. shot with fuji x-t50. usually ramen stores will have different soup bases,
and you make your choice from there with toppings.
the soup bases are typically shio, shoyu, tonkotsu, and miso.</description></item></channel></rss>