<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>freaking weeking</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/freaking-weeking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/freaking-weeking/</guid><description>the last week of december and the first week of january i was lucky enough to have
two four day weekends in a row. which, as you might be able to guess, was absolutely
terrible for work morale. coming back to work has been a slog. but such is the way
of government-observed holidays.
these days, fridays feel so great. there was a tweet that would get reposted
every friday saying &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s the freaking weeking, babey!</description></item><item><title>limbus company</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/limbus-company/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/limbus-company/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve been watching my friend play limbus company recently.
something about a new chapter, called a &amp;ldquo;canto&amp;rdquo;, dropping and that means
more content to enjoy at a rapid pace rather than the maintenance quantity
of gaming that usually comes with mobile games when there isn&amp;rsquo;t something
new to do.
it had me thinking: i&amp;rsquo;m not sure if there&amp;rsquo;s anyone on this world i could
like enough and be interested in enough to pick up a mobile game.</description></item><item><title>chipotle as slop</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/chipotle-as-slop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/chipotle-as-slop/</guid><description>i&amp;rsquo;ve been having a bunch of chipotle recently.
whenever i eat it, i think about how chipotle is now newly referred to as &amp;ldquo;slop bowls&amp;rdquo;.
and to be honest, i like my slop bowl. meat and rice is a staple meal for filipino americans.
however, what i&amp;rsquo;ve concluded is that something in my order of chipotle
is absolutely wrecking my shits afterwards. which, you know, gross, but it&amp;rsquo;s my blog.</description></item><item><title>party finder's newest obsession</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/party-finders-newest-obsession/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/party-finders-newest-obsession/</guid><description>party finder in ffxiv is in an uproar over the state of
prog and clear parties for the recent savage release.
&amp;ldquo;everyone is prog lying. there are tomestone checks everywhere.
it&amp;rsquo;s not fun anymore. parties aren&amp;rsquo;t filling. it&amp;rsquo;s exhausting.&amp;rdquo;
my approach to party finder is as follows:
the opportunity of suffering is only born when you expect something more than what occurs in reality. by understanding that whatever will occur in the party will occur and nothing more than that is destined, i believe you can alleviate the stress of the randomness of the parties.</description></item><item><title>dopamine by lil tecca</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/dopamine-by-lil-tecca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/dopamine-by-lil-tecca/</guid><description>have you listened to lil tecca&amp;rsquo;s 2025 summer album, dopamine? it&amp;rsquo;s a fun one to listen to, starting with the single release of &amp;ldquo;Dark Thoughts&amp;rdquo;,
which is now up to 24M views at the time of writing.
i had heard Dark Thoughts in the past,
but i had never put two and two together in terms of
thinking Lil Tecca could make more songs similar to that
given that it was the single and probably going to be</description></item><item><title>listening to a good podcast</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/listening-to-a-good-podcast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/listening-to-a-good-podcast/</guid><description>i used to listen to a bunch of The Yard
in my free time while driving and playing video games.
however, last year at some point, i stopped because i got more in the mood
for listening to music. i had stopped for long enough that i wondered
if i would ever be able to return to listening to podcasts.
it turns out that it just took a little bit of time for it to come back.</description></item><item><title>bacon review</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/bacon-review/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/bacon-review/</guid><description>i have spent the days since the new year trying out
different store-bought bacon brands to see what&amp;rsquo;s best.
here are my results from worst to best.\
as a preface, i only buy thick-cut bacon.
Oscar Mayer Naturally Hardwood Smoked Thick-Cut Bacon 3.5/5 it&amp;rsquo;s salty and crisps fine. it&amp;rsquo;s classic, but ultimately it&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly small. Wright Hickory Smoked Thick-Cut Bacon 4/5 Wright comes highly recommended by store-bought bacon reviews, but the hickory flavor falls short for me.</description></item></channel></rss>