<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>food on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/food/</link><description>Recent content in food on (´_ゝ`) the gooberverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2024, Gabe Chutuape.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gooberverse.net/blog/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>chipotle's smoked brisket</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/chipotles-smoked-brisket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/chipotles-smoked-brisket/</guid><description>i had the pleasure of trying out chipotle&amp;rsquo;s new protein option,
a returner from years past: the smoked brisket.
if you&amp;rsquo;ve been following the gooberverse, you may remember
that i am a chipotle regular with a consistent order.
however, i am not immune to limited time offerings and the
supernatural pull they have on my humanity and its need to
feel included in the exclusive. far be it from me to defy it.</description></item><item><title>au cheval chicago</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/au-cheval-chicago/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/au-cheval-chicago/</guid><description>if you&amp;rsquo;re in the Chicagoland area,
i would recommend getting a burger from Au Cheval.
they&amp;rsquo;re a michelin-star restaurant that serves
specifically diner fare, but make it gourmet.
they&amp;rsquo;re best known for their burgers which feature
a sunny-side up egg, as well as their garlic aioli.
i took a neat picture of a spotlight at our table
that had a glass of water and some cutlery.
i forgot to take a picture of the actual burger.</description></item><item><title>broccoli cheddar soup</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/broccoli-cheddar-soup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/broccoli-cheddar-soup/</guid><description>broccoli cheddar soup is a beautiful thing.
the melted, slightly salty flavor from the cheese,
the scent of broccoli wafting into your nose,
and the ear-to-ear warmth that a spoonful gives.
i recently rediscovered broccoli cheddar soup
at my local Potbelly sandwich shop on lunch break.
the first time i had broccoli cheddar was
my freshman year of college, six years ago.
i&amp;rsquo;ve never gone out of my way to purchase it,</description></item><item><title>hot chocolate in the summer</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/hot-chocolate-in-the-summer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/hot-chocolate-in-the-summer/</guid><description>hot chocolate in the summer is underrated.
as someone whose favorite season is winter, which is, of course
the season of hot chocolate, i often find myself reaching for a mug
of hot cocoa, especially in the summertime (since winter seems so far away..)
i&amp;rsquo;m not too snobby about my choice of hot chocolate, either.
swiss miss is the classic hot chocolate experience and i think it&amp;rsquo;s fine,
but i&amp;rsquo;ve recently been trying out Ghirardelli premium to great satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>ramen noodles as a meal</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/ramen-noodles-as-a-meal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/ramen-noodles-as-a-meal/</guid><description>do you enjoy eating ramen noodles?
i think part of me romanticizes ramen noodles
because of their association with anime and japan.
ichiraku ramen from Naruto just made it look so delicious.
kyuramen x tbaar wall art. shot with fuji x-t50. usually ramen stores will have different soup bases,
and you make your choice from there with toppings.
the soup bases are typically shio, shoyu, tonkotsu, and miso.</description></item><item><title>boba milk tea</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/boba-milk-tea/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/boba-milk-tea/</guid><description>do you like drinking boba milk tea?
or just milk tea in general?
milk tea is in a weird spot for me as this thing that somehow people view as far more socially acceptable to drink than other similar sweet drinks that are probably outright considered desserts instead of whatever half-category milk teas have carved out for themselves, and it&amp;rsquo;s just interesting to me how far the words &amp;ldquo;milk&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;tea&amp;rdquo; go to carry the elusive nature of their nutrition.</description></item><item><title>korean bbq is wonderful</title><link>https://www.gooberverse.net/korean-bbq-is-wonderful/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.gooberverse.net/korean-bbq-is-wonderful/</guid><description>have you ever been to a korean bbq place before?
i love going with my friends to Mr. Kimchi in Mt. Prospect.
we don&amp;rsquo;t go particularly often, but when we do, i always enjoy myself.
my friends and i at a booth in mr. kimchi, taken on my minolta x-570. korean bbq is where you sit down at a table that has a grill in the center,</description></item></channel></rss>